<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Julien Rousselot</title><description>
  This is a space where creativity meets logic. As a passionate frontend engineer and dreamer inspired by the vastness of space, Leo shares insights on cutting-edge web development, personal projects, and the exploration of new technologies. With a unique blend of technical expertise and a love for innovation, this blog is a journey into problem-solving, design, and the limitless possibilities of the digital universe.
</description><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/</link><item><title>Un Instant Pour Soi</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/how-javascript-is-invovled-in-the-aerospace-industry/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/how-javascript-is-invovled-in-the-aerospace-industry/</guid><description>This project is a showcase website designed for a beauty salon. Developed in React, it highlights the offered services (facial treatments, manicures, massages, makeup, etc.) with a modern and intuitive interface. The site includes clear calls to action, an appointment booking form, and smooth navigation to provide an optimal user experience.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Talk The Globe</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/how-to-make-a-rocket/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/how-to-make-a-rocket/</guid><description>This project is a website for an English and Spanish teacher. It allows users to book online lessons, find teaching materials for educators, and access a payment system to book lessons or purchase materials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MakaraMedia</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/how-universe-was-borned/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/how-universe-was-borned/</guid><description>Makara is a social media content management and sharing platform (TikTok, Facebook, Instagram, etc.). It allows users to centralize their online presence with a customizable digital business card and integrates advanced tools, including AI (Mistral) to optimize media planning. With subscription management via Stripe and a statistical dashboard, Makara offers a complete experience from content sharing to performance analysis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stripe composant</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/payment/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/payment/</guid><description>A Stripe checkout component to perform online payment tests with an interactive visual and the ability to see test results.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LevelWorld</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/rpggame/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/en/rpggame/</guid><description>This project is an online MMORPG currently in development, with a planned release date in 2025. The game allows players to embody a hero in 3D within an open world, built using Three.js, React, and Symfony. In this universe, players can explore, fight monsters, gain experience, and acquire equipment, all directly from their browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Un Instant Pour Soi</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/how-javascript-is-invovled-in-the-aerospace-industry/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/how-javascript-is-invovled-in-the-aerospace-industry/</guid><description>Ce projet est un site vitrine conçu pour un salon esthétique. Développé en React, il met en avant les services proposés (soins du visage, manucure, massages, maquillage, etc.) avec une interface moderne et intuitive. Le site intègre des appels à l’action clairs, un formulaire de prise de rendez-vous, et une navigation fluide pour offrir une expérience utilisateur optimale.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Talk The Globe</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/how-to-make-a-rocket/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/how-to-make-a-rocket/</guid><description>Ce projet est un site web pour une professeure d&apos;anglais et d&apos;espagnol. Il permet aux utilisateurs de réserver des cours en ligne, de trouver du matériel pédagogique pour enseignants, et d&apos;accéder à un système de paiement pour réserver des cours ou acheter du matériel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MakaraMedia</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/how-universe-was-borned/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/how-universe-was-borned/</guid><description>Makara est une plateforme de gestion et de partage de contenu sur les réseaux sociaux (TikTok, Facebook, Instagram, etc.). Elle permet aux utilisateurs de centraliser leur présence en ligne grâce à une carte de visite numérique personnalisable et intègre des outils avancés, dont une IA (Mistral) pour optimiser le mediaplanning. Avec une gestion des abonnements via Stripe et un tableau de bord statistique, Makara offre une expérience complète, du partage de publications à l’analyse des performances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stripe composant</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/payment/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/payment/</guid><description>Un composant Stripe pour réaliser des tests de paiement en ligne avec un visuel interactif et la possibilité de voir les résultats du test.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LevelWorld</title><link>https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/rpggame/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://astro-theme-leo.muji.dev/fr/rpggame/</guid><description>Ce projet est un MMORPG en ligne actuellement en développement, avec une date de sortie prévue en 2025. Le jeu permet aux joueurs d&apos;incarner un héros en 3D dans un monde ouvert, entièrement conçu avec Three.js, React et Symfony. Dans cet univers, les joueurs peuvent explorer, combattre des monstres, gagner de l&apos;expérience et acquérir des équipements, le tout directement via leur navigateur.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>